<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">      There is no help available at this time.</string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">      Help is available for each section of this app.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro">For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
<![CDATA[
       <!-- For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below: --> 
       ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_title_section1">Topics</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
        <!--
     Each help topic has a full page of information. 
     Long topics can be scrolled.
        -->
    </string>
    <string name="broadcast">
<![CDATA[
     <HTML>
<HEAD>
	<META HTTP-EQUIV="CONTENT-TYPE" CONTENT="text/html; charset=utf-8">
	<TITLE></TITLE>
	<META NAME="GENERATOR" CONTENT="LibreOffice 3.6  (Linux)">
	<META NAME="AUTHOR" CONTENT="CA, Inc.">
	<META NAME="CREATED" CONTENT="20130823;20330000">
	<META NAME="CHANGEDBY" CONTENT="CA, Inc.">
	<META NAME="CHANGED" CONTENT="20130823;20330000">
	<META NAME="AppVersion" CONTENT="14.0000">
	<META NAME="Company" CONTENT="CA Technologies">
	<META NAME="DocSecurity" CONTENT="0">
	<META NAME="HyperlinksChanged" CONTENT="false">
	<META NAME="LinksUpToDate" CONTENT="false">
	<META NAME="ScaleCrop" CONTENT="false">
	<META NAME="ShareDoc" CONTENT="false">
	<STYLE TYPE="text/css">
	</STYLE>
</HEAD>
<BODY LANG="en-US" TEXT="#000000" DIR="LTR">
<H1 CLASS="western" ALIGN=CENTER>CA Smart Tracker 1.0 Online Help</H1>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in"><BR><BR>
</P>
<H2 CLASS="western">About CA Smart Tracker 1.0</H2>
<P>CA Smart Tracker 1.0 is a tracking, notifying and alerting
software that can be used by the CA bus commuters who own Android
devices. It works in a collaborative way, where all the commuters who
use this product form a community. It enables all the CA bus
commuters to:</P>
<UL>
	<LI><P>Broadcast the location of their buses.</P>
	<LI><P>Track the locations of all their buses. 
	</P>
	<LI><P>Receive administrative notifications from the CA facilities.</P>
	<LI><P>Send alerts to concerned members against an imminent danger.<!-- How about mentioning ‘this is intended primarily by women employees? 
 --></P>
</UL>
<P><B>Note: </B>CA<B> </B>Smart Tracker 1.0 runs only on Android
devices with OS version 4.2.x or higher. The devices must have Wi-Fi
and internet connectivity<!-- Requires Internet either though Wi-Fi or Mobile data
 -->.</P>
<H2 CLASS="western">How it Works?</H2>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">CA Smart Tracker 1.0 consists of a
client application called Smart Tracker. You must install this
application on your Android device. When you install the Smart
Tracker you become a member of the Smart Tracker community. After
installing the Smart Tracker, you can broadcast, track; send
notifications and alerts for all the commuters.<!-- Sending notifications is not supported right?
 
 --></P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Before starting the Smart Tracker
you must connect to the Wi-Fi device in your CA bus. Your device
sends its location coordinates and the route details through the
Wi-Fi to the Smart Tracker Server (STS). The STS runs in the public
domain. When you enable the “Broadcast” feature on the Smart
tracker, your device starts posting its location coordinates to the
STS periodically. A commuter who wants to track the location of your
bus uses the “Track” feature to track. The Track feature polls
the STS through the internet to obtain the location of your bus.</P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in"><B>Note: </B>Members of the Smart
Tracker community must enable the broadcast feature on their devices.
At least one Smart Tracker member must enable the Broadcast feature
to enable a commuter to track a bus. 
</P>
<H2 CLASS="western">Features</H2>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">When you start the Smart Tracker, it
displays the following four features on the screen of your device.</P>
<H3 CLASS="western">Broadcast</H3>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Click Broadcast to start
broadcasting the location of your bus. It is a toggle UI button,
first click enables the Broadcast feature and second click disables
it.</P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Each broadcast enabled device sends
its location details in the &lt;Latitude&gt;&lt;Longitude&gt;&lt;Route#&gt;
format to the STS. As a result, when commuters start broadcasting in
their CA bus, Smart Tracker members can detect the location of their
respective CA Route buses.</P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in"><B>Note:</B> When more than one
member broadcasts, the tracking commuter gets the latest coordinates.
</P>
<H3 CLASS="western">Track</H3>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in"><A NAME="_GoBack"></A>Click Track to
track of your CA bus. When you click Track, a list of all the bus
route numbers is displayed. Select your Route bus to find its
location. The location of your route bus is shown in the Google map. 
</P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in"><B>Note:</B> If you want to track
your route bus, at least one member traveling in your route bus must
enable the broadcast feature. In case nobody traveling in your route
bus broadcasts, you will not see your route bus in the track list. 
</P>
<H3 CLASS="western">Escort<!-- Looks like we need to rephrase this a little.
We’ll discuss this
 --></H3>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Click Escort to send an alert
message to a configured destination when you are expecting an
imminent danger. It is a toggle UI button, first click enables the
Escort feature and second click disables it. This feature enables
female commuters to send an alert message, and also post their
location for tracking purpose.</P>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Enable the Escort feature while
traveling, and shake your device in suspicious circumstances. Once
you shake your device an alert message is sent to the configured
destination.</P>
<H3 CLASS="western">Notifications<!-- As discussed there are more to talk about this feature but I think that comes in different section

 --></H3>
<P STYLE="margin-bottom: 0.14in">Click Notifications to see any
notifications that are sent to you by the CA facilities.</P>
<DIV TYPE=FOOTER>
	<P ALIGN=RIGHT STYLE="margin-top: 0.92in; margin-bottom: 0in; line-height: 100%">
	1.0</P>
</DIV>
</BODY>
</HTML>
      
      ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_title_section2">Html Text</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">     Learn how to display simple forms of Html in a text view.
     Paragraphs, bold, italics, and links are supported.</string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
<![CDATA[
      <p>
        Track:<br>
      </p>
      	<h1>Displays list of all routes available with location information. Select desired location see the current location of the bus.</h1> 
      <p> 
       <h1> The selected route will be shown in Google maps. You may change the preference to show all ways your default bus route location in maps</h1>
      </p>
      
        
       ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_title_section3">Links</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3"></string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
<![CDATA[
	     <p>
	     	<h1>
	      		eScort is a feature which helps in emergency to protect women employees of CA. Enable this mode when you want send distress signal in emergency to the security dept. it does not require user to unlock the phone 
	      		and click on any buttons in emergency but it just activates by shaking your device in a pattern.
	     	</h1>
	     <p>
	     
	     <p>
	     	<h1>
	      		It will automatically send SMS to pre configured contact numbers, send emergency signal to security message central, makes a call to 1 pre configured number and 
	      		also makes a loud noise to make others aorund you alert about it. 
	     	<h1>
	     <p>
	     
	     <p>
	     	<h1>
	      		Please configure your emergency contact information from settings page. 
	     	<h1>
	     <p>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_title_section4">Buttons</string>
    <string name="help_text_section4"></string>
    <string name="topic_section4">
<![CDATA[
      Notifications:<br>
      <p>
      <h1>
      	You will be subscribed to 1 or more messaging channels(route info channels) to get notified by Facilities/Admin Dept. with emergency
      	notifications. You will be able to see all the notifications pushed from facilities/Admin/security Dept. from here.
      <h1>
       </p>
       
       <p>
      <h1>	Please use options available in settings to configure your notification channels. You can subscribe to all the channels.</h1>
       </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

</resources>